<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Tutorial>
    <Titles>
        <EasyTutorial1>SimAirport 基础教学</EasyTutorial1>
        <Expansion>Large Airport Expansion</Expansion>
        <Baggage>行李系统</Baggage>
        <FuelPA>PA系统与燃油</FuelPA>
    </Titles>
    <EndTutorial>关闭</EndTutorial>
    <NextButton>继续</NextButton>
    <SkipObjective>跳过</SkipObjective>
    <EasyTutorial1>
        <IntroductionTitle>欢迎光临 SimAirport!</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>你正在阅读的是入门教程。

这个教学机场是你通向世界的门户。这个小航站楼拥有最基础的设施：交通、票务、安检、候机室、登机口和行李提取区。

但问题在于：机场中的这些设施 都！没！完！工！</Introduction>
        <CameraMovement>在继续建设之前，我们先来学习如何移动镜头。可用的方法有四种：WASD键、方向键、将光标放置到屏幕边缘、按住鼠标中键并拖动鼠标。

你可以在设置-相机(缩放/平移)下调整相关镜头的移动速度。

你还可以在设置中自定义移动镜头的操作方式。</CameraMovement>
        <TutorialWindow>为避免影响视野，你可以按住鼠标左键不放并移动鼠标以将此教学引导窗口一旁。
        
大部分类似的窗口都可以用上述方式拖拽，同时也都可以通过点击X图标来关闭它们。对于本窗口，你可以点击右上角的“——”来最小化窗口，稍后可以点击“□”来还原窗口。</TutorialWindow>
        <TutorialWindowObjective>任务：尝试拖拽此窗口到一旁吧！</TutorialWindowObjective>
        <UserInterface>这个复杂的机场模拟器可以很简单地上手，先来看看屏幕上的这些按钮吧~

顶部是状态栏，右上角是时间控制，左下一排是机场的操作面板，右下角的按钮可用于调出各种信息的视图。

按下ESC可以关闭任何激活的窗口。（注：此教学窗口不会受到影响）</UserInterface>
        <ConstructIntroTitle>建筑与地基</ConstructIntroTitle>
        <ConstructIntro>SimAirport 中最重要的一个因素就是建筑。

无论是建筑物还是机场设施，都必须由工人进行建造。所有的室内房间必须建造于地基之上，建造完成后，适用于室内的物品才能放置于其中。</ConstructIntro>
        <Hire4Workmen>在你指定某区域为建筑物后，工人们会自动订购所需的建筑材料。

材料会由卡车通过公路运输到机场，于西南角的“运输区”卸货。工人们接下来会将这些材料放置到对应的位置上并开始施工。任何多余的材料，比如规划好后又取消建造而产生的材料，会被放置于“储藏区”。</Hire4Workmen>
        <Hire4WorkmenObjective>教学任务：点击左下角的“员工”按钮(快捷键：KeyboardFunctions.StaffHub)并尝试雇佣工人，使机场内工人总人数达到6。</Hire4WorkmenObjective>
        <DragFoundation>接下来尝试建造地基：点击“建造”按钮，选择二级菜单“工具”，然后点击“地基”。光标悬浮在任意按钮上即会弹出说明性文字。
        
规划一个区域后，工人会前去施工。施工需要一段时间，但你可以调整时间速率来避免无聊的等待：右上角的时间面板的四个按钮从左到右分别是暂停（快捷键：空格）、1/4/10倍速（快捷键：1/2/3）。</DragFoundation>
        <DragFoundationObjective>任务：在条纹状区域（黄色与品红相间）建造地基。（注：如果规划时出了错误，可以选中正在施工的项目-取消项目。）</DragFoundationObjective>
        <BuildingMistakes>除了上述方法之外，你还可以使用“摧毁”工具（快捷键：KeyboardFunctions.DemolishTool）来摧毁地基。

或者，针对错误放置的物品，你可以使用“清除”工具（快捷键：KeyboardFunctions.ClearTool）来清理它们。不确定是哪一类？那么可以尝试按下 KeyboardFunctions.BuildModifier 来自动检测所需的清理工具。</BuildingMistakes>
        <GuestNeedsTitle>需求与区划</GuestNeedsTitle>
        <GuestNeeds>旅客有很多需求：饿了、无聊了、想去厕所了之类的。很惭愧，我们机场目前解决如厕需求的方法还只有洗手间这一项。

解决各种各样的需求有助于提升旅客对我们机场的满意度，我们也可从中获利：更多的航空公司会因而与我们签约。</GuestNeeds>
        <Boredom>游艺区：这是个解决内心无聊问题的好地方。来试着规划一块区域给游艺区吧！

规划区域是为了帮助旅客与员工了解何处可以找到所需的设施。你可以随时按下KeyboardFunctions.ZoneToggle来查看区域划分情况。</Boredom>
        <BoredomObjective>任务：点击左下角“区划”按钮，再将新完工的小房间指定为游艺区。</BoredomObjective>
        <ProblemArcadeTitle>如何解决问题</ProblemArcadeTitle>
        <ProblemArcade>当某个房间出现问题时，其底色会变为红色。将光标悬浮其上以查看解决方案。大部分问题都是区域尺寸问题，或者缺少必须的设施。

按下 KeyboardFunctions.RotateObject 或鼠标中键可以旋转一个物品。从建造/区划按钮中选中物品后，右键单击可以取消选中。</ProblemArcade>
        <ProblemArcadeObjective>任务：尝试修复游艺区目前的所有问题，使其可以正常运作。</ProblemArcadeObjective>
        <EnvironmentTitle>发展机场与各种热图</EnvironmentTitle>
        <Environment>机场环境若是丑陋，可能会导致旅客心情不好。可以通过买一些盆栽来改善环境、愉悦大众。

观赏植物可以在建造-物品-装饰下找到。你同时也可以在建造-建设-地面下购入地板来改变整体样式。

你可以在激活环境热图（位于屏幕右下角，已自动激活）来观察你机场的环境：红色表示亟待改善、绿色表示环境优良。</Environment>
        <Decorate>其余的热图也很有用。

信息热图（位于屏幕右下角，已自动激活）展示了成可以可以从哪里获知有关航班的最新消息。

放置航班信息显示器（Flight info display）、信息亭(kiosk)等物品可以帮助旅客寻找登机口、楼层等，从而避免错过航班。</Decorate>
        <PlaneStandsTitle>修复损坏的停机坪！</PlaneStandsTitle>
        <PlaneStands>我们的机场目前没有任何航班！而要想获得航空公司的合约，我们首先需要让停机坪正常运转起来：与“滑行道”相连、分配到对应的“登机口工作人员台”。

提示：①在建造菜单下搜索类似“滑行”、“工作”的部分关键词可用快速筛选出所需的选项。②完工后，单击登机口工作人员台或停机坪（机舱门）、选择“分配到…”，将二者连接。</PlaneStands>
        <PlaneStandsObjective>任务：将光标悬浮在停机坪（门A1）上以查看其无法正常工作的原因，然后修复这些问题。</PlaneStandsObjective>
        <QueuesTitle>井然有序</QueuesTitle>
        <Queues>为了提升效率，我们应为所有的登机口工作人员台设置队列。

具体操作：在建造-排队下，点击“扩大队伍”，在附近设置一个队伍（比如粉色区域）。然后，点击登机口工作人员台，将其分配到新设置的队伍。

票务区和安检区的大部分设备都可以进行类似的队列设置。</Queues>
        <QueuesObjective>任务：建立一个队列，并将其与登机口工作人员台相连。</QueuesObjective>
        <FlightStatusTitle>没有飞机的机场不是好机场Airports Need Planes!</FlightStatusTitle>
        <FlightStatus>既然我们已经有了一个正常运转的停机坪，那么下一步就是获取飞机来接送旅客了。

打开“航班状态”窗口（已自动激活，快捷键: KeyboardFunctions.FlightStatus），你会发现现在尚无航班。</FlightStatus>
        <FlightManage>打开“航班管理”窗口（快捷键: KeyboardFunctions.FlightSchedule），上半部分为意向的航班合约。目前我们机场只能提供小型飞机(S)的降落场地，所以也只有一家提供小型飞机的公司向我们展示了意向合约。窗口的第二行是筛选器，可以筛选所需的机舱门尺寸和航班到达时间。

如果希望获得夜间航班(PM)的合约，你需要选中跑道，点击“升级”，然后为其添加“跑道灯”。</FlightManage>
        <FlightManageObjective>任务：接受2个航空公司合约，并为它们指定到达/起飞时间（在总飞行时间表中，将这两架次航班从“新航班”拖动至你想要的时间段即可）。</FlightManageObjective>
        <RunwayLength>要想获得大型(L)、超大型(XL)的飞机的合约，你需要建立更大的停机坪（机舱门），并延长跑道的长度。

延长跑道长度的具体方法：打开建造-建设-工具面板，选中水泥跑道/沥青跑道工具，从现有跑道的顶端向同方向延申。</RunwayLength>
        <PlaneLands> 新签订合约的航班会在次日对应时间首次到达，对航班时间的改动也会在次日生效。

如何合理安排时间表是对你的一种考验：航班过于紧凑，则机场过于混乱、旅客与航空公司都不满意；航班过于松散，则机场难有盈利。</PlaneLands>
        <UsefulUITitle>重要信息</UsefulUITitle>
        <UsefulUI>在屏幕顶端，“乘客满意度”与“航公公司利息”两项是相当重要的信息，你可以将光标悬浮于其上以预览信息，也可以点击以查看详细信息。

这两个信息可以提示你如何发展机场才能满足旅客与航空公司的需求。</UsefulUI>
        <WeatherAndUpgrades>屏幕顶部同时还有天气条，天气影响着飞机降落时的安全。

点击跑道，选择“升级”，面板中的部分设施可以在飞机降落时为飞行员提供更准确的指导，从而使得飞机可在更为恶劣的天气条件下安全降落。</WeatherAndUpgrades>
        <FinanceHubTitle>迈向成功</FinanceHubTitle>
        <FinanceHub>机场终究需要盈利。但没准就会出现手头现金不够用的情况：金融中心-银行贷款也许是你的好助手（已自动打开）。

当然，你也可以找到屏幕顶部的“银行余额”按钮，悬浮以查看预览、点击以进入金融中心。</FinanceHub>
        <Research>但部分功能目前是锁定的：你需要进行相关研究并雇佣相关人员以解锁。与其他地方类似，悬浮光标于对应位置即可查看所需的前置条件。

如果所需的员工你目前还不能雇佣，请转到研究面板，进行研究以解锁雇佣他们的资格。不断进行研究来保证你的竞争力吧~</Research>
        <CommercialOperations>另外一项重要的事情是价格。
            
在商业定价（快捷键：KeyboardFunctions.OpsControlPanel）窗口中（已自动打开），你可以调整航空公司使用机场服务的价格。注意：低价意味着航空公司更愿意与机场合作，高价则意味着机场能更好地盈利。</CommercialOperations>
        <FinaleTitle>基础教程·完</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale> 以上即Sim Airport基础教程的全部内容了。接下来你可以尽情扩展这个机场了~
            
你也可退出到主菜单，然后新建一个机场来游玩。另外强烈建议你先完成其余教程，以及在开始新游戏时关闭“从头开始”选项、从内置的初始机场环境开始游戏。</Finale>
    </EasyTutorial1>
    <Expansion>
        <IntroductionTitle>Large Airport Expansion</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the second easy difficulty tutorial.

Large, complex airports can be difficult for passengers to traverse. This can cause them to be late, hurting your ratings.</Introduction>
        <SolutionsTitle>Solutions To Improve Efficiency</SolutionsTitle>
        <Solutions>Solution 1: Manage your queues.

Solution 2: Build a second terminal.

Solution 3: Place moving walkways in long terminals to help passengers move faster.

Solution 4: Build on multiple floors to keep distances short.</Solutions>
        <Tip1Title>Solution 1: Managing Queues</Tip1Title>
        <Tip1>You can assign the same queue to multiple services, such as one queue to three ticketing desks. This is an optimal way of making sure all waiting passengers are served in the order they arrived.</Tip1>
        <Tip2>Sometimes a fair order is not the most efficient!

Creating a seperate queue for flight crew will allow them to bypass the main queue, which is especially useful at security. If the crew arrive late to the plane, it causes delays.</Tip2>
        <Tip3>You may also want to consider having priority queues for first class, as their satisfaction affects your airport rating much more than coach satisfaction does.

Don't skip making queues! Staff get confused about who is next to serve when everyone is crowding around, causing them to be much slower.</Tip3>
        <SecondTerminalTitle>Solution 2: Multiple Terminals</SecondTerminalTitle>
        <SecondTerminal>Multiple Terminals:

If there's enough space, and you have a large enough budget, a second terminal would be great for improving airport efficiency. This allows you to split up airplane gates between multiple security and ticketing zones, as long as they are connected!</SecondTerminal>
        <SecondTerminalProblems>This will require a lot more infrastructure to function correctly. Only do this once you are confident in how to get the first terminal working.

Tip: You could load the default map, and copy it below it to practise making one! Make sure the operational objects are assigned correctly.</SecondTerminalProblems>
        <WalwayIntroTitle>Solution 3: Moving Walkways</WalwayIntroTitle>
        <WalkwayIntro>Building walkways along very long areas of the terminal is the easiest and cheapest way to improve efficiency. This is assuming you have wide corridors to drag them down.

They can also be used by staff and baggage carts! Because each go in one-direction, consider how passengers will use them. Don't build huge ones; leave gaps so people are free to walk off them.</WalkwayIntro>
        <WalkwayTips>Just remember that long walking distances are not the only reason for passengers being late. Make sure to investigate long queues and where people are slowing down.

As explained in tutorial 1, building custom queues allows you to visually identify traffic problems.</WalkwayTips>
        <WalkwayTask>A recommended area has been shown as an example, going from security to the departure lounge. This is recommended because passengers need to get to their flights quickly.

To build them, search "Walkway" in the build menu search bar, and then simply drag in the direction you want it to be built in.</WalkwayTask>
        <WalkwayTaskObjective>Build a walkway, possibly on the recommended area.</WalkwayTaskObjective>
        <FloorsIntroTitle>Solution 4: Multiple Floors</FloorsIntroTitle>
        <FloorsIntro>Multiple Floors:
            
It might not be practical to fit in walkways if there is little corridor space.

Depending on the layout of the airport, there might be no choice but to expand upwards. This is where multiple floors come in.</FloorsIntro>
        <Controls>Use KeyboardFunctions.LevelUp to go up a floor, and KeyboardFunctions.LevelDown to go down. Or, click on the arrows to the right of the screen. This follows the American system: there is no first floor after the ground floor.

Anything you can do on the ground floor, you can do on the other floors (except terrain changes).</Controls>
        <Underground>Underground areas are useful for hiding later complicated systems, such as baggage conveyors and utilities, from passengers. You still need a foundation under where you place objects.

They can also be useful for connecting different areas, such as a terminal-island, via tunnels. You could combine a long tunnel with moving walkways!</Underground>
        <AboveGround>Higher levels can be useful for expanding your shopping areas in the departure lounge, or adding staff zones that are out of the way of passengers.

A second floor door connection is required for the larger gate sizes to connect to the terminal.</AboveGround>
        <SecondFloorOptionalTask>Feel free to build a second floor above the departure lounge, to make room for shops. Remember to connect it with stairs!

Before anything can be built on this floor, a foundation must be placed. That foundation must be placed above an existing one on the lower floor.</SecondFloorOptionalTask>
    </Expansion>
    <Baggage>
        <IntroductionTitle>Baggage Systems</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the first advanced tutorial.
            
Baggage Systems are a must for large airports. This will allow for efficient loading and unloading of plane luggage, and swift deliveries to the Baggage Claim.</Introduction>
        <SmallAirports>Do note that if you are running a small airport, you don't need a full baggage system. To handle baggage you just need ticketing desks, a Baggage Claim zone, and extra workmen.

These workmen will drive baggage carts between the zones and gates to keep up with demand, and this will work fine for small airports.</SmallAirports>
        <SystemIntroTitle>Using Multiple Floors</SystemIntroTitle>
        <SystemIntro>Before you can start building a baggage system, you first have to get used to using multiple floors as demonstrated in the Large Airport Expansion tutorial. We'll briefly cover it here.</SystemIntro>
        <MultipleFloors>Use KeyboardFunctions.LevelUp to go up a floor, and KeyboardFunctions.LevelDown to go down. Or, click on the arrows to the right of the screen. This follows the American system: there is no first floor after the ground floor.

Anything you can do on the ground floor, you can do on the other floors (except terrain changes).</MultipleFloors>
        <UndergroundFoundation>As you can see, the underground foundation has already been built.

When you do this for your own airports, you need enough space for ramps, conveyor belts, and luggage hubs.</UndergroundFoundation>
        <ConveyorRampTitle>Step 1: Ticketing to Planes</ConveyorRampTitle>
        <ConveyorRamp>We need the luggage to get from the ticketing desks to the planes.

A conveyor ramp will deliver luggage between floors.

In the Build Menu, go to the Utilities tab for every baggage-related object (and more).</ConveyorRamp>
        <ConveyorRampObjective>Place a Conveyor Down Transition on the ground floor in the highlighted spot. If it cannot be placed, keep rotating it on that area shown and it should turn green.</ConveyorRampObjective>
        <DeskToRamp>Now we need the desks to be connected to this ramp. The direction is automatic, so it does not matter which way you drag them.
        
Note: if you wish to place things freely, place these objects where you like and skip ahead at any point. If you decide to skip, remember you'll have to figure out how to connect them yourself!</DeskToRamp>
        <DeskToRampObjective>Connect the desks to the ramp with conveyor belts on the highlighted line. You will need to wait for it to be built - remember the speed controls in the top right!</DeskToRampObjective>
        <HubTitle>Sorting The Luggage</HubTitle>
        <Hub>The luggage needs to be sorted. A baggage hub will take inputs, and sort them into outputs. You can rotate it with middle-click or by pressing KeyboardFunctions.RotateObject.

Note where the hub's entrances and exits are, based on the arrows pointing in towards it and out of it. You can right-click on any to change what type they are!</Hub>
        <HubObjective>Build a baggage hub and connect it.</HubObjective>
        <DepotTitle>Finishing Step 1: Ticketing to Planes</DepotTitle>
        <Depot>Once the luggage is sorted, it will need to be sent to a baggage depot close by to the aircraft gates. This is where they will be collected from for planes.</Depot>
        <DepotObjective>Build a baggage depot on the ground floor on the highlighted spot.</DepotObjective>
        <HubToDepot>An output from the baggage hub needs to connect to the input of the baggage depot.</HubToDepot>
        <HubToDepotObjective>Connect the depot to the hub on the highlighted squares as a guide.</HubToDepotObjective>
        <CheckDepotWorks>To check if the connections are correct, hover over the depot. It should no longer require a connection to a ticketing desk.
        
It will only deliver luggage for gates assigned to the depot. This can be taken advantage of when you have large airports with multiple depots.</CheckDepotWorks>
        <CheckDepotWorksObjective>Now click on the depot and assign it to the aircraft gate.</CheckDepotWorksObjective>
        <DepotToPlane>The baggage will not be able to get to the planes yet! Baggage cars will deliver luggage to and from depots. They are stored in hangars.

You can search for "Hangar" in the build menu or find it under structures.</DepotToPlane>
        <DepotToPlaneObjective>Build a small hangar anywhere next to a taxiway, and once constructed, add a baggage car.</DepotToPlaneObjective>
        <DepartureWorks>The baggage car will deliver luggage between the depot and the gates assigned.

That's departure flights sorted, but now we need to sort out arrivals luggage.</DepartureWorks>
        <DepotToHubTitle>Step 2: From Planes to Carousels</DepotToHubTitle>
        <DepotToHub>Firstly, let's get the arrivals luggage from the baggage depot to the hub.</DepotToHub>
        <DepotToHubObjective>Connect the conveyor belts, to match the output of the depot to the remaining input of the hub.</DepotToHubObjective>
        <Arrivals>Now passengers need a way to actually collect their luggage.

They collect these from baggage carousels, which need to be connected underground. It already comes with a ramp in the middle of it.</Arrivals>
        <ArrivalsObjective>In the Baggage Claim zone, add a carousel, which is found in Utilities.</ArrivalsObjective>
        <HubToCarousel>Finally, the luggage needs to get from the hub to the carousel!</HubToCarousel>
        <HubToCarouselObjective>Connect the remaining out of the hub to the in of the carousel.</HubToCarouselObjective>
        <FinaleTitle>Working Baggage System</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>Congratulations, you (assuming you didn't skip) have a working baggage system!</Finale>
    </Baggage>
    <FuelPA>
        <IntroductionTitle>PA Systems and Fuel</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the second advanced tutorial. This tutorial will help make your large airports operate better.

PA systems help stop passengers and flight crew missing their flights, while fuel services will increase the interest of airlines!</Introduction>
        <PAInfoTitle>Public Announcements</PAInfoTitle>
        <PAInfo>Firstly, let's get a PA system working. Let's not lose high ratings on confused passengers.
            
The PA system is triggered twice during the boarding process. First, when the plane begins boarding. Then, it broadcasts a "last call" about 15-20 minutes before departing.</PAInfo>
        <TechnologyTitle>Unlocking PA</TechnologyTitle>
        <Technology>You need to research Technology in order to be able to hire a CTO (Chief Technology Officer) and unlock the PA systems.

While you are waiting for it to research, you can build an office for your future CTO. During the tutorial, research is much faster than normal!</Technology>
        <TechnologyObjective>Research Technology in the research screen.</TechnologyObjective>
        <CTO>Once you have a CTO and an office, you will be able to unlock PA systems.</CTO>
        <CTOObjective>Hire a CTO and make sure that they have an office.</CTOObjective>
        <SpeakersTitle>Building the PA System</SpeakersTitle>
        <Speakers>Speakers relay announcements across the terminal. Passengers need to be close to a speaker, and in the direction of a speaker, to hear it.
        
As you are placing them, use the PA Speakers heatmap to see the area that they affect.</Speakers>
        <SpeakersObjective>Place at least 4 speakers in areas most likely to be visited by passengers. Use the PA Speakers heatmap to see coverage.</SpeakersObjective>
        <Amplifier>PA Systems use amplifiers to connect the speakers to a central electrical system.

If you have more than 4 speakers or more than 4 gates, build a HD amplifier to handle the additional load.</Amplifier>
        <AmplifierObjective>Drag an electrical zone room, and place an amplifier inside. Make sure it meets the requirements.</AmplifierObjective>
        <Connect>You'll need to connect each speaker to the amplifier, by clicking on the amplifier, and selecting Connect To.

At the moment, your PA system will be broadcasting nothing! You can assign up to four gates that you want it to broadcast information about, by clicking on the amplifier and assigning each one.</Connect>
        <CompletedPATitle>Fueling Services</CompletedPATitle>
        <CompletedPA>Your PA system should now be working!

Next, we'll look at fueling services.

Refueling planes helps your airport earn extra income, improve airline satisfaction ratings, and potentially get access to new contracts.</CompletedPA>
        <FuelDepotTitle>Getting The Fuel</FuelDepotTitle>
        <FuelDepot>Fuel is delivered once per day, to a depot where delivery trucks will deliver new fuel from outside of the airport.</FuelDepot>
        <FuelDepotObjective>Build a fuel depot by the main road.</FuelDepotObjective>
        <FuelTanks>Fuel is stored in fuel tanks. Large fuel tanks are available, but are very expensive. They need to be connected to the depot, and you can save on piping by building them close.

You can see which pipes have fuel if they are red (empty) or green (full/connected to depot).</FuelTanks>
        <FuelTanksObjective>Build at least two regular fuel tanks and connect them to the depot.</FuelTanksObjective>
        <RefuelingStationTitle>From Storage to Planes</RefuelingStationTitle>
        <RefuelingStation>Trucks will drive along the taxiway to a refuel station to fill up.</RefuelingStation>
        <RefuelingStationObjective>Build a refuel station next to the taxiway, and connect it to the rest of the fuel network with pipes.</RefuelingStationObjective>
        <Transport>It's time to buy the trucks that will do the work. You'll need to build a hangar first, and buy the truck from the hangar's menu.</Transport>
        <TransportObjective>Buy at least one fuel truck.</TransportObjective>
        <BuyFuelTitle>The Business of Fuel</BuyFuelTitle>
        <BuyFuel>Go to Operations, and click Fuel Services. You can buy fuel and sell it. If you keep an eye on the market price and are shrewd enough, you can make a profit dealing fuel!</BuyFuel>
        <BuyFuelObjective>Buy at least 10000 fuel. You can purchase this once, or set it to auto-purchase every day.</BuyFuelObjective>
        <Active>If you find that the status of fuel services is "Not Active", try hovering over it to see what problems there are.

You will need to set a price scheme. Try each one; there is information below each one to help you choose which pricing method is better.</Active>
        <MoreInfo>Make sure to scroll down the fuel services window to see more information.

In future, you may want to upgrade your aircraft gates to have fuel ports, which will more efficiently delivery fuel to your planes.</MoreInfo>
        <FinaleTitle>Working Systems!</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>You now have working PA and fuel systems!</Finale>
    </FuelPA>
</Tutorial>
